<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><TooltipTypes xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><TooltipType Name="TEMPLATE"><Header>The Header</Header><Text>The Text</Text></TooltipType><TooltipType Name="ACCOUNT"><Header>All Your Cool Stuff and Excellent Progress</Header><Text>See your levels, achievements, and stats. Manage inventory, watch replays, and more.</Text></TooltipType><TooltipType Name="PLAYGAME"><Header></Header><Text></Text></TooltipType><TooltipType Name="STORE"><Header>Browse Custom Skins, Taunts, and More</Header><Text>You will look good. New shipments arrive all the time. Sorry, no pay to win items.</Text></TooltipType><TooltipType Name="MISSIONS"><Header>Earn Bonus Gold For Completing These Missions</Header><Text>Every week you'll get new missions that reward you for exploring new legends and playstyles.</Text></TooltipType><TooltipType Name="SOCIAL"><Header>Friends List</Header><Text>All your Steam friends who play Brawlhalla are here. Chat, spectate, team-up, join a game room, and more.</Text></TooltipType><TooltipType Name="OPTIONS"><Header>Technical Options</Header><Text>Customize your controller or your keyboard controls. Also set volume, full-screen, and more.</Text></TooltipType><TooltipType Name="COUCHPARTY"><Header>Play Offline with up to Four Controllers</Header><Text>Tips: Hit 'Brawlers' in the upper left to set teams and bots. Hit the 'Settings' Button to set game modes.</Text></TooltipType><TooltipType Name="SINGLEPLAYER"><Header>Single Player Modes</Header><Text>Go for a personal high score in the Tournament or check out the advanced tools in the Training Room.</Text></TooltipType><TooltipType Name="ONLINEFFA"><Header>Online Matchmaking Queue</Header><Text>Jump into a 1v1 strikeout or four-player, free-for-all brawl. And stay classy in the chat.</Text></TooltipType><TooltipType Name="CUSTOMONLINE"><Header>Create or Join an Online Game Room</Header><Text>Play, spectate, and hang out. Create a game room and share the room number with your friends.</Text></TooltipType><TooltipType Name="RANKED1V1"><Header>1v1 and 2v2 Ranked Queue</Header><Text>Not for Beginners. Win with grace, lose with class. Have fun. It's a long way to the top.</Text></TooltipType><TooltipType Name="BUGREPORT"><Header>Tell Us About Bugs</Header><Text>Thanks! We're in beta and adding features all the time, so we really appreciate your bug reports.</Text></TooltipType><TooltipType Name="LORE"><Header>Each Legend is Legendary For a Reason</Header><Text>Learn a bit about each legend's life before a Valkyrie offered them a place in Brawlhalla.</Text></TooltipType><TooltipType Name="NEWSPAGE"><Header>The Latest News</Header><Text>Also, check out the Brawlhalla Community Hub on Steam for full patch notes, tournament info, discussion, and more.</Text></TooltipType></TooltipTypes>